const STORE = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following defines the term 'raster'?",
    answers: [
      "File with limited colors",
      "Grid of x and y coordinates on a display space",
      "Resizable graphic file",
      "Graphics with infinite scalability"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Grid of x and y coordinates on a display space"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a shade of color?",
    answers: ["Red", "Blue", "White", "Navy-Blue"],
    correctAnswer: "Navy-Blue"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a design principle?",
    answers: ["Scale", "Balance", "Proportion", "Emphasis"],
    correctAnswer: "Scale"
  },
  {
    question: "A logo is loosely defined as what?",
    answers: [
      "A watermark",
      "A way for designers to market themselves",
      "A minimal image or graphic",
      "Graphic or symbol of a company/abbreviation"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Graphic or symbol of a company/abbreviation"
  },
  {
    question: "The human eye is drawn to which area first?",
    answers: ["Center", "Top Right", "Top Left", "Bottom Left"],
    correctAnswer: "Top Left"
  },
  {
    question: "A graphic designers primary aim is toâ€¦",
    answers: [
      "Display unique style",
      "Please users/viewers",
      "Effectively communicate a message",
      "Design attractive material"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Effectively communicate a message"
  },
  {
    question: "Which color profile is best for full color printing?",
    answers: ["RGB", "Monochrome", "CMYK", "None of The Above"],
    correctAnswer: "CMYK"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which file format should be used for transparent image elements?",
    answers: ["PNG", "PDF", "TXT", "JPEG"],
    correctAnswer: "PNG"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which application is best used for designing a print document with several pages?",
    answers: [
      "Microsoft Word",
      "Adobe Photoshop",
      "Adobe InDesign",
      "Microsoft PowerPoint"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Adobe InDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a serif font?",
    answers: ["Times New Roman", "Helvetica", "Arial", "Comic Sans"],
    correctAnswer: "Times New Roman"
  }
];